[ Mac ]
He really has an ugly face.
[ Dennis ]
Mmm, he does.
He is certainly ugly.
But you know what?
That's not really what
bothers me about this.
What bothers me is that he
looks like an old woman.
Right!
[ Dennis ] Yeah.
[ Mac ]
Well, he is wearing...
a lot of blush
on those cheekbones.
Right!
But I feel like that
was the look of the times.
It's not just that though, Mac.
It's not. I mean,
a lot of presidents somehow
end up looking like women.
I mean, look at
Ronald Reagan. Right?
Mm-hmm.
- He looks--
- Why would you hang a painting
like this on your wall?
It's the historical society,
bro. They have to hang it up.
Right. Yeah.
We gotta suffer just because
some old dude who looks
like Meryl Streep...
chopped down a cherry tree
10 million years ago?
It's just--
He looks terrible!
You know what?
Let's take it down.
It's just gonna distract us
through the meeting.
Yeah. Let's get it down, man.
Let's take it down.
I'm gonna tear it down.
[ Mac ] It's gonna distract us.
Unbelievable.
It's bolted to the wall.
That proves our point, man.
We're not the first people who
tried to take that thing down.
Yeah, but we're gonna be the
first ones to actually succeed.
Let's tear it down, Charlie.
Let's just rip it
off the wall!
Whoa! Guys, guys, guys!
I got a pocket knife.
Just cut it out of the frame.
[ Dennis ] That's a good idea.
I've had enough of this dude.
Just cut it
right out of the frame.
What are you doing?
Oh. Uh--
Do you want this up?
Yes. Yes, I do.
Really?
- Uh, may I help you gentlemen
with something?
- Yeah. Yeah.
Actually, we're here because
we want to get our bar certified
as a historic landmark.
We want tourists to be able
to come by Paddy's Pub as part
of the walking tour of Philly.
You know, they can come by,
soak up some history,
do some shots, get blasted.
In order to be considered
as a historical site,
your bar would have to have
some historical significance.
Trust us when we tell you that
Paddy's Pub played an extremely
important part in history.
Mm-hmm. And what part
of history might that be?
The cracking of
the Liberty Bell,
of course.
So you're claiming
that your bar...
had a direct role
in the cracking
of the Liberty Bell?
- Absolutely.
- Then tell me about it.
Well, the year was 1412--
Oh, ooh. Oh, ooh, no.
Really?
Let Dennis-- Let Dennis--
-Let me tell the story, Charlie.
-Okay. [ Clucking Tongue,
Imitating Hoofbeats ]
Yeah. The year was 1776.
And Paddy's Pub, then known,
of course, as Patrick's Pub,
was a hotbed
of revolutionary activity.
Revolutionaries from all over
the country had come together
to gather at Patrick's Pub...
to speak of war
and revolution.
Will you look at that?
Sons of Liberty--
patriots meeting in our bar
speaking of revolution
and freedom.
Can you believe it,
dear Brother? We're witnessing
history in the making.
I do not give a shit, Deandra.
Now get me a flagon of ale.
Get your own ale, dick.
Uh-uh!
You are my slave.
You have to get me
flagons of ale.
I saved you from being
burned at the stake
for being a witch!
You're the one who
accused me of being a witch
in the first place, Dennis!
Oh, well, what's done is done.
That's all in the past now.
So you can either be a slave
witch in the bar or you can be
a burned-up witch outside.
Up to you!
Flagon of ale now?
Guys, guys, guys!
I've got some news.
I've got some terrible news.
Oh, MacDonald,
how goes it?
Not good.
You know that chick
I've been banging
down at Independence Hall?
- Mmm, the fat one.
- Well, she's not that fat.
She's pretty fat, dude.
Good one, witch. [ Laughs ]
Pretty fat.
Well, whatever.
She told me
in complete confidence...
that a bunch of old dudes
down there are drafting
a declaration--
a declaration of independence.
Wait. Why would we want
to be free from the British?
This declaration is gonna
start an all-out war.
We have to make sure we are
not on the losing side!
Definitely.
Okay, clearly the British
are gonna win this thing.
Clearly.
All right. We have to make
sure that the crown knows
that we're on their side.
We have to make
our own declaration.
Yes.
Yes. We need to make
a declaration of dependence.
[ Chattering ]
Buy your pelts here.
We have raccoon.
We have foxes.
Oh!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Ho there, sir.
Now, my good gentleman, what
says you of my fine furs here?
Mmm!
Merrily, I be able to guide you
towards some interest
in some purchase?
I can't understand
what you're saying.
You wanna buy a fur?
Yeah!
In July? No, thanks.
Whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Not so fast now.
It's a nice-looking cart
of pumpkins you got here.
Mmm!
Uh, what says you we maketh
some trade, hmm? All of my furs
for all your pumpkins?
No.
All right.
I-I-I-I-I-I--
One pumpkin.
Deal.
All right then! [ Chuckles ]
Wait, wait, wait!
Whoa, Charlie, Charlie, Charlie!
We're not traders, Charlie.
We're thieves.
You want his pumpkins?
We kill him
and take his pumpkins!
This is 1776!
We'll get away
with it!
I can hear you.
Yeah, all right. Very good.
This is how it will go down.
I will beat the man...
about the face and the neck
and maybe the chest area
and possibly the groin--
Eh?
until he's no longer
consisting of life pulse.
And then you can collect up
the man's cart.
I shall findeth a stick.
Yes! Well, we'll need
a stick to do the bashing.
Sit tight, sir.
Pick a stick.
Any stick you like.
All right.
Methinks the rod to be the most
suitable for our purposes.
Ahh! Very nice rod.
Go with that rod.
Okeydokey-dokey-doo!
Uh-oh! He's gone.
What! He stole our furs!
Yep. Yep, yep, yep,
yep, yep, yep.
You shithead!
Hey, look on
the bright side, Franklin.
We got ourselves
a pumpkin.
[ Dennis ]
This is gonna work.
[ Mac ] I can't believe
you dressed like that, bro.
Excuse me. This is a good plan.
Okay? If we're gonna
get this declaration
into the hands of the queen,
we need to dress the part.
That's not the way
the British dress, bro.
They dress like this.
No. British commoners
dress like you're dressed.
British peons. Okay?
I'm dressed like a nobleman,
okay?
These people respond
to royalty.
[ Dee ]
Hey. Hey, guys.
- Come on. Please help.
- Just use your witch strength,
slave.
Yeah. It's not
that much further. God!
Uh, pardon me.
Pardon me, good sirs.
Which of you gentlemen happens
to be the highest-ranking
military officer here?
That would be me.
Cricket.
Colonel Cricket.
- Hmm.
- What is your business, sirs?
Ah, well, Colonel, we are
the owners of the fine local
establishment, Patrick's Pub.
Ahh. Patrick's Pub.
Yeah.
Yes, of course.
Of course.
The liberty bar, huh?
You harbor patriots.
Oh, whoops.
No, no, no.
No!
No, nayeth.
Nayeth.
Bad intel there.
Yeah, bad intel.
Bit of a miscommunication.
Yes. Yeah.
Actually,
that is why we're here.
Uh, we drew up this declaration.
We also included
an illustration that we
had hoped would illuminate...
our intentions
towards the queen, huh?
This appears to be
a rendering of the two of you...
sodomizing the king--
Huh?
whilst the queen
is forced to witness.
Oh!
Goodness gracious, no!
No! No! Look. I'm holding
homeboy's arms back.
Yeah.
Dennis is ready
to jam him in the face.
The queen is impressed.
Yeah. That's a bad guy.
That's not the king.
-We're doing bad stuff
to the bad--
-Give me this. You don't get it?
Let's get the ale. The ale.
Wench, now the ale.
Presenteth it.
Okay, set that down
in front of him.
And yes, good Colonel,
we present this ale to you and
your men in hopes that it will
fuel the British to victory.
Madam.
- Whoa! Hey!
What the hell are you doing?
- Come on!
- Get out of here! You're making
things worse! Flee! Fly!
- Get back to the bar!
I'm really sorry.
That was huge.
Yeah.
- That hit you right in
the face, didn't it? Oh, man.
- Yeah, you know what?
We don't condone
that sort of thing, okay?
No.
We're gonna tar and feather
the shit out of her when
she gets back. Don't worry.
I pray you,
who is that fiery wench?
Her? Oh, that's just
my sister, Deandra.
She's our slave.
Yeah. And a witch.
Yeah.
- You keep your sister
as your slave?
- Oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah. Aye.
[ Laughs ]
So are we good here now?
What's the deal?
Gentlemen, you have both proven
to me in the very short time
that I have known you...
that you are both
slanderous perverts...
lacking any semblance
of moral fortitude.
However, I do desire to seek
further counsel with the lady.
The... lady?
Uh, the-- the witch?
The same girl we've
just been talking about?
You don't really think
she's a-- a witch, do you?
Yeah. Yeah,
she's a witch.
I-- Yeah, I'm pretty sure.
Pretty sure.
All right, look.
I wish to court her
in some manner,
and I could use your help,
because I'm not, admittedly,
very good with women.
Good "with" women?
You mean, good at women?
Like you can't catch them
when they run away from you?
Bro, it's 1776.
They don't have any rights.
You can just take 'em and force
'em to do whatever you want.
I do not wish to take her.
I would like to win her favor,
like a gentleman does a lady.
That just does not
compute with me.
I don't understand
what you're saying.
Diggin' the accent
but don't understand you.
Are you saying you're gay?
All right!
Escort them out!
Oh, no. We-We-We-- Okay.
Are you gonna
drink the beer?
No. Leave it. Out.
Just drink the beer.
Maybe you'll get some balls
and you can take the woman.
Yeah.
All right.
Well, I'm just saying.
Higher.
Ready?
Yes.
All right.
Shoot.
One, two--
Whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
three.
Do not shoot
that pumpkin!
What are you doing?
I stole a bunch of guns.
I'm testin' 'em out,
Charles.
This revolution
is gonna make us a fortune.
All right. Well,
leave the pumpkin out of it.
The pumpkin's innocent.
[ Frank ]
Shoot the pumpkin.
Do not shoot the pumpkin,
please.
Okay.
Give me the gun.
Fine.
And why is the witch slave
shooting at you anyway?
- Maybe she used her sorcery.
- Sorcery? Your dumb dick
partner walked into the bar,
said he stole a bunch of guns
and asked if I wanted to shoot
a pumpkin off his head.
Of course I did,
so here we are.
Damn your necromancy,
woman!
Oh, my God.
Maybe if we shoot you,
you won't feel it anyway, witch.
Yeah. Shoot her.
You know what? Okay, you guys.
I tell you what. You win.
I'm a witch, okay? I'm a witch,
and I curse both of you
and all of your stupid guns.
[ Clicks ]
[ Screams ]
Charlie! Goddamn it!
Give me that gun!
It didn't work!
She cursed the gun!
She cursed the gun.
[ Clicks ]
She put a curse
on the gun!
Let's try this one.
[ Clicks ]
Nothin'!
Try me!
[ Clicks ]
[ Chattering ]
Man, those Sons of Liberty
sons of bitches, Dennis.
Those guys are gonna get us
in so much trouble.
Let's do this.
No, no, no, no!
You hang back.
What? Me? Why?
[ Teeth Whistling ] Because
we need to get as much intel
from these guys as we can...
for that
Colonel Cricket.
Yeah?
This fop thing's gonna
totally blow our cover.
What's goin' on with your mouth?
I got some
wooden teeth put in.
Did ya?
Yeah. All the patriots
are doing it,
including Washington,
which is why it makes sense,
okay, if we're going undercover!
Not this fop bullshit!
No. The fop thing's good, man.
I got a plan with it. Yeah.
Got an angle.
Fine. Okay, listen.
You let me
take the lead, okay?
Yeah, okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
You son of a bitch.
Fellas! How you doin'?
A couple of flagons of ale
for ya.
[ Chuckling ]
So I just want to say we love
what you're doing over here.
I mean, taxation with
representation, right?
So, uh, what's the buzz, huh?
What are we all talking about,
huh?
[ Effeminate
British Accent ]
Surrender maybe?
W-We speak of revolution.
Revolution? Revolution?
That's great!
I'm completely on top of that!
[ Laughs ]
Hey, fellas, who's taking
the minutes here?
'Cause I feel like I could be
an asset to you as a secretary.
Yes.
Let's start by taking down
all of their names,
first and last, please.
- Son of a bitch.
- Gentlemen, I think
this meeting is adjourned.
Huh?
[ Clears Throat ]
Son of a bitch, dude!
What are you doing with
the accent and the Briti--
Goddamn it!
No, I just decided to go
a different way. The spy thing
wasn't really working.
Yeah? What way was that?
Your wooden teeth, whistle-y
tooth thing? That was bad.
I think my teeth
were a smashing success.
We are in dire straits here.
We need a change of plans.
I think the only way we're gonna
convince these people...
that we're on their side
is to become
a hundred percent British.
Become British?
We gotta commit
to the fop thing.
That actually seems
pretty sensible, Dennis.
Yeah. No more S's for you.
[ Mouths Words ]
It's just
so cramped in here.
I mean, you'd think people
who came here so many years
before the English--
You'd think they'd
build bigger houses.
- Yeah, you'd think they'd
have huge homes, right?
- Yeah!
What is the sleeping situation
in here? You think this father
and son are sleeping...
on the same bearskin together?
Probably. Where else
are they gonna sleep?
What a bunch of losers!
Oh, I'm telling you.
It's a bunch of inbred savages.
I speak English.
Oh, shit! For real?
- Yes.
- Oh, that's not good.
We didn't mean to--
Our bad then. Hey, so tell me.
How much land are you gonna give
away for a pumpkin these days?
W-Wait, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Charlie, Charlie, listen. What
we need is your magical powers--
Yeah.
to lift the curses
from our guns.
[ Imitates Gunshots ]
Okay?
We're gonna pay ya.
Oh, yeah.
We gotta pay ya.
We'll give you this.
- We brought this for you.
- Booze!
Booze.
Right? Makes you feel good.
Helps you sleep.
Brings the tribe together.
[ Speaking Native Language ]
Ooh! Oh! That young Indian
was fast with the tomahawk.
And he really lobbed a big
hunk off your head up here.
Oh, yeah.
It's gonna make me
look deformed.
Yeah.
You're gonna be deformed
for the rest of your life.
Gimme that skunk pelt.
I'll use it for hair. Don't
push, don't push, don't push!
[ Dee ] All right.
Does it look cool?
It looks pretty good.
- Lady Deandra.
- Yes? Can I help you?
Colonel Cricket.
We met the other day?
I was the one
you delivered the keg to?
You spit in my face.
Oh, yep, yep.
There it is. Mm-hmm.
[ Chuckles ]
Indeed.
Forgive my rather
unadorned approach, but--
Mm-hmm.
from the first moment
I laid my eyes on you--
Mmm.
I was smitten.
Mm-hmm.
Perhaps my impatience
has gotten the best of me,
but if you will have me,
I would be most honored...
to call you my wife.
Oh! [ Coughs ]
A simple "no"
would have sufficed.
[ Laughing ]
Hey, hey.
Okay. All right.
That one got in my mouth.
That's really not cool.
You listen to me, you pale-faced
English dick-hole.
You got a revolution coming.
And pretty soon all
of the slaves are gonna be free,
and I will be owned by no man.
I am a fool--
Yeah.
having allowed myself to imagine
us back in my sprawling manor
in England.
You on my arm adorned
in magnificent garments, dressed
in the finest jewels, and--
Whoa, whoa, Cricks. Back it up
a little bit. You're talking
about garments and jewelry?
But alas,
my love cannot mend
our differences.
Oh, no.
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Your love-- Your love can.
Your love is-- Your love
is currently doing that.
So you just--
You didn't mention anything
about the sprawling manor
and all the garments.
That was stupid.
I thought you
just said that you--
Yeah, I di-- I did, I did.
But it's-- Your love,
it's like-- [ Grunts ]
It's filling me up with
all kinds of stuff, and--
Is it?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it is!
Let's do this!
What?
Let's get married!
Yeah!
[ Chuckles ]
Oh, Lady Deandra.
Yes!
You have made me
the happiest man alive!
Eww!
We're gonna have
to work up to that, though,
'cause you are crazy ugly.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Keep your pants on, curly.
Yeah.
You want the slave?
You gotta pay
for the slave!
What?
I'm sorry?
We're not gonna give her
to you for free.
Yeah.
You gotta sweeten the pot.
Huh?
[ Blows Raspberry ]
How'd you like
to buy some guns?
Yeah.
Guns?
- I shall buy your guns.
- [ Dee ] Yes!
I shall buy your guns!
No, no, no, no.
Not yet. Not yet.
Hey. Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey.
[ Spits ]
[ Groans ]
Why does he keep
spitting in my mouth?
[ Spits ]
Who is this man?
[ Squealing ]
[ Dennis ]
Ah, hello to you, sirs.
And to you, ladies.
These heels are almost
impossible to walk in.
Get over it, dude.
You gotta walk in them, okay?
Now let me hear the voice.
[ Teeth Whistling ] No. I don't
think the voice is entirely
necessary. I'm not gonna do it.
Bro, if we're gonna wipe away
all traces of our colonial
background and blend in...
with British culture,
we need to walk the walk
and we need to talk the talk.
Fine. How do you do it?
Your voice needs to come off as
elegant as your clothing, okay?
So try this. [ Clears Throat,
British Accent ]
Would you like a spot of tea?
You: Ye-e-e-e-es!
[ British Accent ]
Would you like
a spot of tea? Ye-e-es!
Draw it out more.
Draw it out
more than that?
Oh, yes. Ye-e-e-e-es.
More than that.
Ye-e-e-e-es!
Yeah, but--
That's good.
You know what?
Those wooden teeth are
killing me. That lisp is stupid.
I think the wooden teeth
are the whole thing
that's saving this thing.
You sound ridiculous.
No, I don't. I think
it sounds pretty good.
I'm not losing the teeth.
Let's just move past that.
Let's keep walking.
Okay, try it again,
try it again.
Ye-e-e-e-es!
[ Laughs ]
Good, good, good.
Now flourish the pinkie.
Flourish the pinkie.
Ye-e-e-e-es!
Well, what have
we got here?
A pair of poofs
about town.
Sodomites
in frilly lace.
Oh! No, no!
No! Nayeth!
Oh, nayeth, nayeth! No!
Nayeth, no!
We are simply two noble
British men out on a stroll.
Yes, yes, yes.
Good day, sir.
Good day!
Oh, goodness.
Oh.
[ Chuckles Weakly ]
- Boys, get the tar.
- [ Both Chuckle ]
Shit.
- [ Gunfire In Distance ]
- Deandra, come and help me
count my gold.
I'm not your slave anymore,
Franklin.
I'm about to go live like
the goddamn queen of England and
never see you two bitches again.
Charles, I told you
the revolution pays.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
But look at this, huh?
Guys, there is a full-fledged
revolution happening outside
right now!
- It is a bloodbath!
We have got to do something!
- Whoa! Whoa!
What?
Let's back up and talk
about what this is.
No, this is not
important right now!
Oh, I think it's very important!
There's a war
happening outside.
We were acting like British
nobleman. Then he couldn't
drop the she-male thing.
[ Gunfire Intensifies ]
So we got tarred and feathered
for being sodomites!
Well, it is not--
[ Stammers ] a she-male thing.
[ Mocking Stammer ]
It's about-- Goddamn it!
We don't have time for this!
[ Gasping ]
Help!
- Help me!
- Are you okay? Are you dying?
No, no! Don't die yet!
Don't die yet until you
get me to your mansion!
No. I'm unscathed,
my darling.
Oh, thank God.
This is the blood
of my men.
Yeah.
We suffered
too many casualties.
All our guns jammed!
Blame that
on your witch wife.
Let me see that.
Permit me to hide out here till
British reinforcements arrive...
and massacre
the entire lot of rebels.
Then shall we escape
safely together, my darling.
Oh! Okay. I'm gonna
go get you some water.
Hey, Cricks? When the
reinforcements get here,
Dennis and I are cool, right?
We're not on your shit list.
Yeah. Like we got tarred
and feathered for your ass. So--
Protect me and I shall make sure
that all of you are safe
from the mighty sword of Bri--
- [ All Gasp ]
- Oh, shit!
Goddamn it, Frank!
You just ruined
my whole life!
Wait, wait, wait.
Check his pulse.
[ Dee ]
He doesn't have a head!
[ Mac ] Oh, my God!
If the British come in here and
find this body, we are screwed!
Jesus, God, he's right!
We gotta get rid of this body!
How are we gonna do that?
Maybe we could bury it out back.
No, there's no time.
We gotta burn that body.
Burn? It's gonna call
too much attention!
Let's chop it up
into a million pieces!
I got an idea.
Careful man. Steady.
[ Grunts ]
It's heavy.
- [ Front Man ]
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
- [ Bell Clangs ]
Shit!
Bro, we just broke
the Liberty Bell.
I'll get you, my pretties!
[ Cackling ]
Pretties!
It's totally broken!
Stop... this... story!
- Okay?
- We weren't quite finished yet.
We were just climaxing there.
I've finished listening.
Have you now?
[ Both Groan Softly ]
Uh, okay.
Well, that's fair.
Uh, the end, I guess.
Uh, so are we
an historical landmark now?
- No!
- You gotta be kiddin' me.
It's such a good story.
Yeah.
Maybe she didn't
understand the story.
Maybe we skimmed too much.
Well, let's tell the full story
this time. Let's-- We won't
leave out any details.
A lot more details.
You know what? Sit back.
Get comfortable.
This is gonna take
a little longer this time.
Okay.
You ready?
It starts the same.
Okay.
The year was 1776--
[ Voices Speaking Backwards ]